const data = [
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Kallini' ",
    options: ["Ilagay", "Gusto", "Basahin", "Laro"],
    correct_option: "Gusto",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Magatag'",
    options: ["Kumuha", "Kailangan", "Magbigay", "Sabihin"],
    correct_option: "Magbigay",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Pagbarin'",
    options: ["Pag gamit", "Pag lipat", "Pag bigay", "Pag kuha"],
    correct_option: "Pag lipat",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Lawngan' ",
    options: ["Tulungan", "Sabihin", "Gamitin", "Kunin"],
    correct_option: "Sabihin",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Surat'",
    options: ["Sumulat", "Sinabi", "Basahin", "Gamitin"],
    correct_option: "Sumulat",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Mayroon'",
    options: ["aw gayd", "kay nanga", "awb", "Ipanglaong"],
    correct_option: "awb",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Salita' ",
    options: ["nilawngan", "puaglawngan", "Ipanglaong", "all of the above"],
    correct_option: "all of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Gawin'",
    options: ["inangon", "kanami", "kang", "kipat"],
    correct_option: "inangon",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Gumagana'",
    options: ["yagalihok", "yaga gana", "yaaandar", "all of the above"],
    correct_option: "all of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Maglaro' ",
    options: ["paballong", "yaaandar", "kang", "aw gayd"],
    correct_option: "paballong",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Ilagay'",
    options: ["paballong", "butangan", "yagalihok", "kay nanga"],
    correct_option: "butangan",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Pagbabago'",
    options: ["Kabaguwan", "Kanlini", "Kay nanga", "kamang"],
    correct_option: "Kabaguwan",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Kailangan' ",
    options: ["Kailangan ", "kanlini ", "kinahanglan", "all of the above"],
    correct_option: "all of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Kumuha'",
    options: ["Kamang /", "yakamang / ", "Kamanga", "all of the above"],
    correct_option: "all of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Pag-imo'",
    options: ["Gumawa", "Pagsulat", "Para sayo", "Pag tingin"],
    correct_option: "Gumawa",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Ilawng' ",
    options: ["Sinabi", "Binuksan", "Oras", "Gumagana"],
    correct_option: "Sinabi",
  },
  {
    question: "TRANSLATE: 'Basa'",
    options: ["Basain", "Basahin", "Ilagay", "Ibago"],
    correct_option: "Basahin",
  },
];

export default data;
